척이예요
몇 가지 아셔야 할게 있어요
Previously on "Chuck"...
There are a few things
you might need to know.
- 척한테 다신 상처주지 마세요
- 네
- Don't hurt him again.
- I won't.
The hotel's booked,
호텔 예약해뒀으니까
차 안 막히면 금방 갈거야
so we should probably go
if we're gonna beat traffic.
With this list,
it's just a matter of time
이제 풀크럼 요원
명단을 얻는건 시간문제야
before we learn the identities
of FULCRUM's agents.
척, 경치 좀 봐
정말 멋있다
Chuck, look at this view!
It's amazing.
척, 그냥 관람차야 걱정하지마
Chuck? It's just a Ferris wheel. It's fine.
??
2002년, 캘리포니아 팔로 알토
응 알았어
Yeah.
얘가 나보다
네 맘을 더 빼앗는구나
Yeah, it's not the...
it's not the wheel so much as it is me.
응? 무슨 소리야?
What? What does that mean?
우리가 꼭대기에 있을 때
세워달라고 돈을 좀 쥐어줬거든
I kind of sort of bribed the carny
to stop us at the top.
Well, for someone who's afraid
of heights, that was pretty moronic.
고소공포증 있으면서
바보같이 왜 그랬어
I was going for...
로맨틱한 분위기 좀 내려고 한건데..
romantic,
그게..
그래 말할게
Okay, here goes.
질, 우리 둘이 친구로 지낸지
이제.. 한 학기쯤 됐지?
Jill, we... we've been friends for...
for, like, a semester now, right?
정말 재밌게 지냈잖아
And it's been really fun.
그래서 말인데..
And I was just... I was thinking
that maybe, you know,
그래서 혹시나..
혹시나.. 너랑 나랑..
you and I... we could,
I don't know...
모르겠다
있잖아, 네 말이 맞아
You know what? You're right. I-I...
대체 무슨 생각을 한거지?
What am I thinking? You're right.
This is moronic. I...
맞아. 진짜 바보같다
You were happy being friends,
and I'm happy being friends,
너도 나도 서로 친구로 잘 지내니까
- and I just thought...
- Chuck,
그래서 혹시..
척, 이게 문제야
there is a problem.
넌 말이 너무, 너무 많아
You talk way, way too much.
질 로버츠가 풀크럼 요원이라고?
Jill Roberts is FULCRUM?
근데 척을 데리고 있어?
And she has Chuck?
How is that possible?
어떻게 이런 일이 생길수가 있나?
르플뢰르의 명단을 해독하는중에
Well, the LaFleur List
contained a code name
our computer translated
to one Jill Roberts.
풀크럼 요원 중 한 명이
질 로버츠라는걸 알게됐습니다
하지만 그 땐
이미 둘이 떠난후였어요
By the time we saw it,
they were already gone.
His cell is switched off, and
his watch is still in the apartment.
척 핸드폰은 꺼져있고
시계는 집에 두고 갔습니다
Find him. I don't care how.
Just do it.
찾아내게. 방법은 상관없어
찾아내기만 하게
이젠 소용없어
You know, it doesn't matter.
이미 풀크럼에서 고문하고 있을거야
FULCRUM's working him over about
now. He's not gonna last an hour.
- 한 시간도 못 버틸걸
- 아니. 아니야
No, you're wrong.
그 쪽에선 척이
인터섹트인걸 모르잖아
They don't know Chuck's the Intersect,
우리가 질 정체를
알아차린것도 모르고
and they don't know
Jill has been burned.
Well, if it ain't torture...
고문이 아니면
대체 뭘 하고 있는거지?
what are they doing to him?
바토스키씨, 당신 입을
열 방법이 있어요
We have ways to make you talk,
Mr. Bartowski.
마음대로 해보세요
Do your worst.
There's gonna be yelling.
보나마나 혼날거야
여기 온거,
혼날 가치가 있었어?
Well, was it worth it?
Was it worth it?
가치가 있었냐고?
It was so worth it.
엄청 가치 있었지
난 가서 샤워하고 올게
I'm going to take a shower.
You deal with the yelling, okay?
넌 혼나고있어
응
Okay.
씻고와
??
Oh, that's not good.
이런. 진짜 혼나겠다
Jill, your phone's buzzing.
질, 문자 왔어
응?
What?
??
안돼 안돼
Oh, no. No, no, no, no!
??
This can't be happening.
말도 안돼
What was that, Chuck?
뭐라고 한거야, 척?
아니야
Nothing!
아무것도 아니야
nothing at all, actually.
I was just saying, I'm a little...
저기 내가 좀...
I'm a little, uh, parched,
내가 좀 목이 말라서
그게..
'cause-cause, well,
last night was incredible.
어젯밤이 굉장했잖아
You know? Like,
we had some fun, didn't we?
그치? 어제 재밌었잖아?
Then I was thinking,
hey, you want some coffee?
커피 마실건데 너도 줄까?
Yeah, that'd be great.
응. 나도 마실게
응, 응 알았어
Okay, great, great.
이 멍청아!
You idiot!
이 멍청하고 바보같은 놈아!
You sad-sack,
bleeding heart idiot!
질이.. 질이..
She's-She's...
Chuck, never do that again.
척, 다신 이러지 마요
It's Jill. I think....
질이.. 질이요..
- We know.
우리도 알아 / 알아요
잠시만요
Wait.
뭔가 오해가 있는거예요, 네?
This-This has got
to be a mistake, okay?
I've known Jill
for eight years, since college,
질하고 대학 때부터
8년째 알고지냈어요
and we-we had this really amazing...
그리고 어제, 어제, 정말
즐거운 밤을 보냈다고요
...night.
스파이일리가 없어요
Look, she's not a spy, and
she has no FULCRUM code name.
게다가 풀크럼 암호명도 없어요
- The code name was...
- Wait, wait, wait.
- 암호명은..
- 잠시만요 안돼요 말하지 마세요
- Don't say it.??
- Sandstorm.
샌드스톰
말도 안돼
Oh, my God.
질이 스파이예요
Jill's a spy.
유감이예요
I'm sorry, Chuck.
다시 방으로 돌아가라니
무슨 소리예요?
What do you mean
I have to go back in there?
Think, Bartowski.
생각 좀 해. 우리가 알아차린걸
질이 알아선 안돼. 알겠어?
We don't want Jill to know that
we know she's a spy, right?
Oh, okay, look, okay.
네 네 알겠어요
질은 풀크럼 요원이예요
Jill is FULCRUM.
풀크럼에선 인터섹트를 찾고 있고요
FULCRUM is looking for the Intersect,
근데 그 인터섹트가
나잖아요!
and the Intersect just happens
to be me.
척, 그 쪽에선 그걸 몰라요
Chuck, they don't know that.
Trust me. We're right here.
Everything will be fine.
날 믿어요
우리가 여기 있을거니까
다 괜찮을거예요
안전해요
- You will be safe.
- Yeah.
그래, 힘내게 병사
Buck up, soldier.
FULCRUM pulled one on us.
풀크럼에서 우리 쪽으로
파고 들었으니
Let's return the favor.
우리도 갚아줘야지
??
Thank you, sweetie.
고마워 자기
천만에 자기
You're welcome... darling.
Chuck 2x08
Chuck Versus the Gravitron
chuck S02 ep08
www.1000fr.com presents
재커리 리바이
(척 바토스키 役)
Sync:FRS@밟駒
이본느 스트라호브스키
(새라 워커 역 役)
조슈아 고메즈
(모건 그라임즈 役)
라이언 맥파틀린
(캡틴 짱 役)
마크 크리스토퍼 로렌스
(빅 마이크 役)
스캇 크린스키 / 빅 사하이
줄리아 링
새라 랜체스터
(엘리 바토스키 役)
아담 볼드윈
(존 케이시 役)
Chuck, are you sure
everything's okay?
척, 정말 괜찮은거 맞아?
응? 당연하지
정말 괜찮아. 정말이야
Yeah. Everything's fantastic. It's great.
This is me on the verge
of total happiness.
나 지금 무지 행복해
그럼 됐어
오늘밤에 만날까?
Okay, do you want to do
something tonight?
음 그게 나도 그러고 싶은데
yeah, I would... I would love to,
but the problem is,
그게.. 집은 위험해
the apartment is not safe.
My sister's back,
and I can't blow my cover, so...
누나가 돌아왔는데
누나가 내 정체를 알면 안되니까..
Well, we can go out.
그럼 밖에서 만나면 되지
그래. 그렇게 하자
Okay. All right.
Okay.
잘 가
운전 조심하고
Bye.
Drive safe.
괜찮아요?
Are you okay?
처음에는, 모든게
달라질거라 생각했어요
You know, for a few days, I thought
things were going to be different.
나만의 인생을 갖고
여자친구도 사귀고
I could have a life.
I could have a girlfriend.
평범한 사람처럼 될 수 있겠구나..
I could be a regular human being.
I thought Jill was...
그리고 질은..
- Different?
- No. Normal.
다를줄 알았다고요? / 아니요
평범할줄 알았어요
어떻게 이런 일이 생기죠?
How could this happen?
Jill must have been recruited
when she was at Stanford.
질은 스탠포드에 다닐 당시
채용된 것 같네
풀크럼에선 요원 후보를 찾아내려고
리더쉽 세미나를 이용한다더군
FULCRUM uses leadership seminars
to look for possible agents.
잠시만요 죄송해요 장군님
대체 스파이 아닌 사람이 누군가요?
Excuse me, I'm sorry, General,
but who in my life isn't a spy?
My sister? My best friend?
우리 누나?
제일 친한 친구?
처음 만나는 사람마다
물어봐야 하나요?
Should I just start asking people
that when I first meet them?
Hi. I'd like the extra value meal,
안녕하세요
더 주문하고 싶은데요
and while we're on the topic,
말이 나와서 말인데
혹시 정부에서
do you covertly work for
a government espionage faction?
비밀리에 첩보요원으로 일하시나요?
Your flash in Jill's room
referenced an agent called Leader.
자네가 봤던 메시지에
리더라는 요원이 있다고 했었지
We want you to use
your relationship with Jill,
자네는 질을 이용해서
see if she makes contact with him.
질이 그 요원과
접촉하는지 살펴보게
General, Chuck is not ready
for this type of mission.
장군님. 척은 아직 이런 임무를
수행 할 준비가 되지 않았습니다
질과 헤어지는것도
힘들어 하고 있어요
He could barely handle
a good-bye with Jill.
질은 분명 알아차릴겁니다
She's going to see right through him.
This is our best opportunity
to infiltrate FULCRUM,
풀크럼에 파고들 좋은 기횐데
자네가 척이 아직
준비되지 않았..
but if you don't think he's ready...
할게요
I'll do it.
질은 두 번이나
절 배신했어요
Jill betrayed me twice.
저도 똑같이 해줄거예요
You bet I'll do it.
앉지마!
- ??Don't sit down!
- What? What? What? What?
왜? 왜? 뭐야? 왜 뭔데?
What? What? What is it?
데븐네 부모님이
추수감사절이라고 내일 오실거야
Devon's parents are coming
tomorrow for Thanksgiving,
그니까 쇼파는
완벽해야해
and the couch is...
perfect. Okay, perfect.
좋아 완벽해 / 캡틴네 가족?
The Awesomes?
The Awesomes are coming here?
여기 오신다고?
응. 여기로 오기로 했어
Yes, the Very Awesomes
are coming here.
그 분들이 아들 하나는
잘 키우셨잖니
They make their son
look mildly impressive.
누나, 걱정할 필요없어
Sis, you got nothing to worry about.
누날 맘에 들어하실거야
They love you.
너도 의사, 네 부인도 의사고
I guess when you're a doctor,
and you marry a doctor,
완벽하게 짱인
아들 셋까지 있다면
and you raise three awesome boys,
너도 사람들한테
가혹하게 대할걸
you tend to judge people
a little harsher.
I guess that's how I feel
when Mrs. Awesome is around.
짱네 어머니하고 같이 있으면
그런 기분이 들어
I have never heard you use
the nickname that many times.
누나가 그 별명
이렇게 자주 부르는거 처음 들어봐
나도 알아
괜찮아
I know. I know. It's okay.
지금 좀 스트레스 받아서 그래
I'm just a little stressed right now,
but we all have our burdens to bear.
하지만 우리 모두
참아내야지
야 척! 나야
Hey, Chuck,
yo!
척!
Hey, yo!
응?
What?
있어?
Anybody here?
Like whom?
누구말이야?
누구냐니?
??
Like, the other woman, dude.
여자 없냐는거지
질 말이야
Jill.
모건, 여자 아무도 없어
Morgan, there is no other woman.
Really?
그래? 잘 됐다
That's great, 'cause I thought
방해해야겠다 싶었거든
I was gonna have to do some
sort of intervention or something.
매력적인 여자들한테
중독된 것 같길래
You know, help you with your addiction
to really attractive women.
이 냄새 뭐야?
What's that smell?
누나가 뭐 만들어
probably Ellie. She's doing some
practice cooking for tomorrow.
내일 식사 준비하느라
연습중이거든
맞아. 내일
추수감사절이지
Naturally.
Tomorrow's Thanksgiving.
So, that smell is...
그럼, 이 냄새는...
칠면조구나
turkey.
모건?
Morgan?
모건?!
Morgan?!
이것 좀 먹어봐
I need you to try this.
천국의 맛이예요
It's heaven.
No. No, it's too...
it's too dry.
아냐 아니야
너무.. 너무 말랐어
시험 칠면조 1번, 너무 마름
Test turkey #1 is too dry.
3시간 7분 소요
three hours, seven minutes.
뭐 하는거예요?
안돼 안돼 안돼, 누나
What are you doing?
No, no, no, no.
Ellie, what are you...?
세상에
Oh, my God.
모건
우리 얘기 좀 해
Morgan, we need to talk.
알겠어요. 다신 칠면조한테
그런 짓 하지 마세요
It's fine. Please just don't
hurt another turkey like that.
모건, 이번 추수감사절은
정말 정말 중요해
Morgan, this Thanksgiving
is very important.
Sure.
그럼요
모든게 순조롭게 이뤄져야해
And things need to run smoothly.
알아요 알아요
I know. I know.
You've been so stressed.
너무 스트레스 받지 마요
다 괜찮아요
Everything's great. It's perfect.
What can I do?
모든게 완벽해요
뭘 도와드려요?
모건? / 네?
- Morgan?
- Yeah?
너...
You're...
초대 못 받았어!
??Not invited!
말도 안돼
I can't believe this. I mean, how?
Uninvited to T-day...
아니, 왜?
추수감사절에 초댈 못 받다니..
모건, 모건 진정해
Morgan, Morgan, relax.
I don't know how many times
I have to tell you.
내가 얼마나 더 얘길 해줘야 돼
다 괜찮아질거라니깐
It's all going to be okay.
내가 누나한테 잘 얘기해서
올 수 있게 할게
I'm gonna talk to Ellie,
and we're gonna sort it out.
애나도 여기 없고
너네집이 내 유일한 희망이었는데..
Anna's out of town,
and you guys were my only hope.
- 추수감사절에 너마저 없다면..
- 모건! 모건, 심호흡해
- If I don't Thanksgiving with you...
- Morgan! Morgan, breathe.
Hi. Can I help you?
- 어떻게 도와드릴까요?
- 그라임즈, 따라와
Grimes! With me.
Okay.
네
Did I just hear you don't
have Thanksgiving plans?
추수감사절에 아무 계획이 없다고?
That's terrible, damn terrible.
안됐군
정말 안됐어
이렇게나 많은 직원들이
계획이 없다니 놀랍군
I'm amazed to find
so many staff members
without proper plans for Thanksgiving.
저 불쌍한 녀석들도 계획이 없대
Like these two poor creatures.
Sir, are you inviting us to dinner?
매니저님. 그럼
저흴 초대해주시는거예요?
아니
말 같지도 않은 소리
No...
God, no.
추수감사절에 외로운 놈들끼리
가게 잘 지키고 있어
I need you lonely bastards to stand
guard here at the store on Thanksgiving.
가겔 지켜요?
- Stand guard?
- Yeah, because of Black Friday.
그래. 블랙 프라이데이잖나
그래서 가게에
상품들이 굉장히 많아
We have more product in the store
than ever before,
and you three are gonna
make certain nobody steals it.
그러니 셋이서 도둑
안 들게 감시 잘하고 있어
- 받아
- 전화 또 오면요
Answer it.
Not on the first ring.
제가 별로 기분이 안 좋다는걸
암시하는거예요
It implies an eagerness that
I'm not really feeling right now.
안녕 안녕 안녕, 질
Hi, hi, hi, Jill.
데이트?
A-a date?
오늘 밤에? 응
좋은 생각이네. 어디서?
Tonight? Yeah,
sounds... sounds great. Where?
비밀이라고?
It's a surprise.
당연하지
내가 요원들한테
Of course I can tell my bodyguards to
take the night off so we can be alone.
우리 단 둘이 있을 수 있게
Just the two of us.
밤엔 따라오지 말라고 할게
I'm looking forward to it as well.
나도 기대돼
왜 이래요?
What are you doing?
What was that for?
- 왜 때려요?
- 쪽쪽 소리
The kissy noise. Have
some self-respect, Bartowski.
남자가 되가지고 자존심도 없냐
You're a man.
I got to go talk to Sarah.
새라랑 얘기 좀 해야겠어요
왜요, 왜 그래요?
What... what is it?
새라, 나 좀 도와줘요
Sarah, I need your help.
오늘 어떻게 해야되죠?
How am I gonna survive tonight?
뛰어난 스파이는
표적이 원하는게 뭔지 알죠
Well, a good spy knows
what their mark wants.
우리가 질에 대해
아는게 뭐가 있죠?
And what do we know about Jill?
질은 스파이고,
척이 자기한테 푹 빠져있길 바랄거예요
She's a spy; she wants you
to be under her spell.
- 알겠어요. 어떻게 하죠?
- 질이 시험하려 들거예요
- Okay, how do I do that?
- She's gonna test you.
적당한 때가 되면 당신이 정말
When the time is right,
she's gonna make certain
that she has you, that you love her.
자신을 사랑하는지
확인하려 할거예요
그걸 어떻게 하는데요?
How is she gonna do that?
척이 가장 드러났을때요
When you're most exposed.
감정적으로요
Emotionally exposed.
친밀한 상황있잖아요
키스할 때 같이요
Like a... an intimate moment,
say, a kiss.
Okay. Imagine that I am Jill.
자, 날 질이라고 생각해요
지금은 로맨틱하고
The moment is romantic.
She's close to you.
질은 점점 다가가면서
당신의 눈을 바라봐요
She's looking into your eyes.
네 알겠어요
Got it, okay. You got... I-I got that.
당신이.. 알겠어요
퍽이나 로맨틱한 비밀 기지에
신경 안 쓰려고 노력중이예요
I'm trying not to be distracted
by the oh-so-romantic secret base.
집중해요, 척
Concentrate, Chuck.
계속 내 눈을 봐요
Keep looking into my eyes.
Don't look up.
올려다 보지 말고요
눈을 못 마주치겠으면
입술을 봐요
And if you can't hold Jill's stare,
look at her lips.
좋아요
Good.
머리를 귀 뒤로 넘겨줘요
Now, move her hair back over her ear.
And when you start to kiss,
그리고 키스를 시작할 때
다시 질을 봐요
focus again on her.
And just before your lips
are about to meet,
입술이 닿으려 할 때쯤
눈을 감아요
close your eyes.
좋아요 잘했어요
Okay, good.
이제 다 준비 됐네요
Good, you're all set.
네?
아 네. 준비됐어요
- yeah, good.
- Hey.
이봐
NSA just picked up a purchase
on Jill's credit card.
NSA에서 질 신용카드
사용 내역을 잡아냈어
Two tickets to some stupid concert
down at the Music Center.
뮤직 센터에서 하는
무슨 콘서트 티켓 2장이래
또 망할 오페라나 아니었음 좋겠네
Better not be another freaking opera.
Well, we'll be there waiting for you.
우린 거기서 기다리고 있을게요
척, 질은 무슨짓이든 하려
할거라는걸 명심해요
Look, just remember,
Jill is capable of anything.
You look great.
오늘 예쁘다
Sorry to keep you waiting.
기다리게 해서 미안해
So, what do you
think of my surprise?
어때 깜짝 놀랐지?
우리 원래 여기 말고.. / 응?
??weren't-weren't we supposed to...
What?
Nothing, nothing.
아냐 아무것도 아니야
If I seem tense, it's just
my irrational fear of carnivals
내가 쓸데없이 카니발 무서워하잖아
- acting up on me.
- Oh, right.
긴장이 돼서 / 아 맞다
Come here. I've got
another surprise for you.
이리 와봐
또 놀래켜줄게 있어
여기 올지 알고 있었지?
You saw this coming, didn't you?
돈 쥐어줬구나
You bribed a carny.
You know what happens next?
그 다음엔 어떻게 되게?
너가 아주 아주 긴장을 하고
You get really, really nervous,
and then you ramble on
for a couple seconds, and then...
얼마동안 정신없이
얘길 하는거야. 그리고..
난 너한테 키스를 해
I have to kiss you.
미안해 척
I'm sorry, Chuck.
뭐가?
For what?
What are you doing?
뭐하는거야?
나 풀크럼에서 일해
I work for a group called FULCRUM.
You know who they are,
don't you, Chuck?
너도 그게 어딘지 알지?
널 제거하는게 내 임무야
I plan to eliminate you.
- 질, 제발 이러지마
- 나도 이러고 싶지않아
Jill, please don't do this.
Believe me, Chuck. I don't want to.
I'm not a killer.
정말이야
난 살인자가 아니야
This isn't what I do for a living.
- 내 직업도 아니고
- 총을 들고 있으면서
You pull that trigger,
and it is what you do for a living.
그게 네 직업이 아니라고?
You already broke my heart.
넌 이미
나한테 상처를 줬어
근데 날 쏘기까지 해야겠어?
Is it necessary for you
to shoot it as well?
네 말이 맞아
You're right.
Okay, Chuck, here's the truth.
알았어, 척
사실대로 말할게
There's a FULCRUM operative down
there. He's watching us right now.
지금 저 밑에
우릴 지켜보고 있는
풀크럼 요원이 있어
내가 널 주차장에 있는
차로 데려가기로 했어
I'm supposed to transport you
to a car in the parking lot,
그 사람들 계획대로 안하면
너랑 나 둘 다 죽이려 들거야
and if I don't follow their plan,
they're gonna eliminate
you and me as a precaution.
곧 뮤직센터에 도착해
We're almost to the Music Center.
What's the ETA on Chuck
and the FULCRUM agent?
걔네 있는 곳까지 얼마나 걸려?
잠시만. 놓쳤어
Wait, I lost him. His signal
just dropped off the grid.
신호가 사라졌어 / 뭐?
- What?!
- It was a ghost.
여기가 아닌거야
차 돌려, 케이시 어서!
Turn us around, Casey, now!
뮤직센터가 아니야
They're not at the Music Center.
North 101. Go!
101번 North 도로로 가!
척, 내가 말한대로 해야해
알겠지?
Chuck, you have to
do exactly what I say, okay?
내 카니발 공포증이
내 예전 여자친구들한테 잘 옮겨
I think you should know that
my completely rational fear of
carnivals has spread to ex-girlfriends.
내가 널 믿어야한다고?
I mean, how do I know I can trust you?
How do I know you're not just
gonna take me to the parking lot
네가 날 주차장으로 끌고가서
무슨 짓을 할지 내가
어떻게 아냐고? / 안돼
to do something you said you wouldn't?
Oh, no.
그 사람이야 / 뭐? 그 사람이라니?
It's him.
Who's him? Him who?
리더
Leader.
Okay, come here.
이리와
실례합니다, 처음 뵙는분
길을 막고 계시네요
excuse us, person we don't know,
you're blocking us.
His handlers are closing in.
척 관리자들이 오고 있어
제거해
Eliminate him.
네? 여기서요?
- What, here?
- Don't think.
생각할 필요없어
머리에 한 방 쏘고 가자고
Shoot him in the head and let's go.
방금 뭐.. 뭐라고..
Did-did you...
did you just say...
Let's talk about this first.
먼저 얘기부터 해요
??Think I should just leave
if there's a...
전 그냥 가는게 좋을..
This is a test, Jill.
이건 시험이야
어서 해
Do it now.
너무 늦었어
Too late.
자네 지금 큰 실수하는거야
You're making a big mistake.
죄송해요!
Sorry, sorry, excuse me!
운영 일시 중지
??
바토스키
Mr. Bartowski.
You need to come with me.
나랑 같이 가줘야겠어
질한테 날 쏘라고 했잖아
you told Jill to shoot me.
Why would I ever
go anywhere with you?
근데 내가 당신하고
어딜 같이 가?
I'd rather not leave your body
here on the ride.
여기에 자네 시체를
버리고 가고 싶진 않아
What if some kid saw it?
꼬마가 보기라도 하면 어떻게 해?
Wow, that's, uh...
그것 참..
이상한쪽으로 사려가 깊으시네
that's strangely considerate of you.
딱 지금 내 기분이야
That's exactly how I feel.
척. 날 믿어야해 / 질?
- Chuck, you have to trust me.
- Jill?
해치지 않을거야
I'm not gonna hurt you.
어딨어?
Where are you?
질, 너 어딨어?
왜 이런 일을 하는거야?
Jill, where are you?
Why are you doing this?
풀크럼에 왜,
언제부터 일했어?
When did you join FULCRUM and why?
스탠포드 다닐 때부터야
It started at Stanford.
풀크럼에서 리더쉽 세미나를
후원했었거든
They sponsored a leadership seminar.
After school, whatever job
we wanted, they got us.
졸업 후에, 내가 하고 싶었던
일을 다 할 수 있게 해줬어
꿈을 이루게 해준거지
They made our dreams come true.
빠져나올 순 없었어?
Couldn't you get out?
척. 누군가 네 삶을
속속들이 통제한다면
When someone controls
every part of your life, Chuck,
you have to do what they say.
그 사람이 시키는대로
할 수 밖엔 없어
After a while, I found myself doing things
I never thought I would have done, but...
그리고나서 보니
절대 하지 않을거라
생각했던 일들을
하고 있는 날 발견했지
하지만 그 땐
이미 너무 늦었었어
but then it was too late.
뭐가 늦었다는거야?
Too late for what?
질?
Jill?
질!
Jill!
나 좀 놀랐어, 바토스키
I'm impressed, Mr. Bartowski.
I wasn't really certain
you were a spy, but...
자네가 스파이란걸 믿기 힘들었는데
이젠 알겠군
now I see.
??
잘 가게
Good-bye.
come on.
척, 서둘러
??
꼼짝마!
Don't move!
No, no, wait, wait, wait!
안돼요! 잠시만요!
그러지 마세요
Don't hurt her.
She saved my life.
절 구해줬어요
So one more time, what's the plan?
자 다시 한번.
어떻게 하라고?
We stay here in the store all day.
하루 종일
가게를 지킵니다
무슨 일이 생기면
매니저님께 전화걸고요 / 좋아
Anything goes wrong, we call you.
Good. Remember, you three are
the last line of defense against...
명심해. 자네들이
마지막 방어선이니까
Yeah, but, can I...
this is a bit overkill.
네. 하지만..
좀 지나친 것 같아요
지나치다고?
- Overkill?
- Dude.
야 / 그라임즈
내 첫 번째 가게는
Grimes, my first store was
The Husky Lad: Big and Tall.
덩치있고 키 큰 남자들을
위한 가게였어
"For the more than average man."
평범함을 넘어선 사람들을
위한 곳이었지
88년 추수감사절에
도둑이 들었어
It was robbed.
Thanksgiving of '88.
That was a dark day, Morgan.
정말 힘든 시기였어, 모건
버뱅크에 있는 가게들은
크리스마스를 바지 하나 없이 보냈네
Husky lads throughout Burbank
went without britches for Christmas.
새해가 오기도 전에 망했어
The store closed before the new year.
그러니.. 아니네
So, no...
지나친게 아니야
it's not overkill. It's business.
해야할 일을 하는거지
알겠습니다
Sure.
저흴 두고 가시지 전에
but before you lock us in,
여기 이렇게 있는거에 대해서
법이나 규정 같은거 없나요?
isn't there some sort of law or rule
about locking us in the store?
- I mean, what if there's a fire?
- I'm not worried about a fire.
만약에 화재라도 나면요?
난 화재 걱정은 안해
도둑이 들까봐 걱정이지
I'm worried about thieves.
좋아. 빅 마이크 여사가
식구들과 요리중이야
All right, Lady Big Mike
is cooking with the family;
난 가서 고기 잡아야해
I got fish to catch.
Lady Big Mike?
빅 마이크 여사?
다 괜찮을거야
Everything's going to be all right.
Answer all of our questions
with a "yes" or "no."
질문에 대한 답변은
모두 네, 아니오로 해주세요
Okay.
네
이름이 질 로버츠인가요?
Is your name Jill Roberts?
Yes.
네
??
스탠포드 대학교를 졸업했습니까?
Did you attend Stanford University?
네
Yes.
??
제가 추가 질문 해도 되요?
Can I ask a follow-up question?
넌 빨리 나가기나 해
You're about to leave
through that window.
저 추가 질문 안해도 되요
I rescind my follow-up question.
분자 생물학에
학위가 있습니까?
Do you have a degree
in molecular biology?
네
Yes.
??
풀크럼 요원입니까?
Are you a FULCRUM agent?
아니요
잠시만요
No. Wait...
죄송해요
I'm sorry.
Telling the truth is new to me.
사실대로 말하는게
익숙치 않아서요
네
Yes,
풀크럼 요원입니다
I am a FULCRUM agent.
당신의 풀크럼 관리자, 리더의
최근 행방을 알고 있습니까?
Do you know the current whereabouts
of your FULCRUM handler,
codename Leader?
- 풀크럼 관리자, 리더의 최근..
- 네
Do you know the current whereabouts
of your FULCRUM handler...
- Yes.
- Give us the location now.
당장 어딘지 말해
Tell me now or I lose my calm.
- 어서 말해 인내심이 바닥나기전에
- 질
Jill. Jill, just tell, just tell him.
Please, just tell him.
질
어서 말해 어서
말해 제발
Okay, I'm not supposed to know this,
알았어. 난 원래
알아선 안되는 사실이지만
but FULCRUM has
a mobile medical unit.
풀크럼엔 이동 의료 시설이 있어요
You'll find Leader recovering in an office
building in downtown Los Angeles.
LA 시내에 있는 사무실 건물에서
치료 받고 있을거예요
함정인가요?
Is this a trap?
아니요
No.
??
??What about Jill, Sarah?
새라. 질은 어떻게 되는거예요?
I know what you're thinking.
무슨 생각하는지 알아요
That Jill is the same person
that you went to school with,
저 사람이 당신이
학교를 같이 다니고
데이트도 했던 그 사람 맞아요
and the same person that you dated.
But we cannot be certain.
하지만 확신할 순 없어요
Trust me, Chuck.
내 말 들어요, 척
질을 믿어선 안돼요
You can't trust her.
Is he setting a trap?
- 쟤 지금 함정 만드는거야?
- 응
우리 친구 제프리가
약 15년동안 하는 짓이지
Good friend Jeffrey's been doing
this job for, give or take, 15 years.
This is his Thanksgiving tradition.
추수감사절 전통이야
Amazing.
몇 개나 설치하는거야?
How many traps does he set?
Just the one trip wire,
it's kind of sad.
딱 한 개. 줄만 설치해
좀 슬프지
He tripped over it last year.
작년엔 지가 걸려 넘어졌거든
Anyway, bon app?it, buddy.
어쨌든
맛있게 드시게나, 친구
Turkey in plastic? No, no.
인스턴트 칠면조?
안돼. 이건 아니야
Les, this is all wrong.
레스터, 이래선 안돼
This is not what Thanksgiving's
about. This is pathetic. Dude.
이건 추수감사절이 아니야
가엾잖아. 친구 / 왜?
What? What else is there?
뭐가 또 있는데?
이것보단 훨씬 많지
There's so much more.
Man, yeah, there's-there's fun,
and food, and friends.
재미있고(Fun), 음식에(Food)
친구들까지..(Friends)
And that's, that's just the Fs.
F 천지야
(앞에서 말한 Fun, Food, Friends)
어디에?
Where?
저 밖에
Out there.
Morgan,
모건, 우리 못 나가잖아
we can't leave.
만약에 내가 가지고
다시 들어오면?
what if I could bring it back here?
칠면조말이야
A turkey.
- We, we...
- No, not-not, not like this.
우리 여기 칠면..
아니 이런거 말고
진짜 칠면조? / 그래
- A real turkey?
- Yes!
진짜.. 칠면조를 얻으려면
뭘 하면 돼?
What do I have to do to get this...
real turkey?
모터 꺼졌어
밀어
motor's off. Come on.
야 우리 더 세게 밀어야 돼
Dude, we got to push harder here.
하고 있어
- I'm trying.
- I'm trying. Come on.
노력중이야 / 좀 열려라
This is such a fire hazard.
이래서 불이 나는거야
- Look, look, look.
- Okay, okay.
Hold, hold, you got to hold it.
잡아 잡아 꽉 잡아
제프!
Jeff!
문 열어 제프!
문 열어줘!
- Open the door, buddy.
- Open the door.
알았어
- Okay.
- Oh, my Lord.
맙소사
- Jeff!
- Got it.
제프! / 알았어
그래 잘했어 제프
Okay, nice, Jeff.
Now can you open the door that
is currently chopping me in half?
자 이제 날 절단내려고 하는
문을 좀 열어줄래?
이런 실수했다
My bad.
Did he make it?
나갔어?
Security breach at Buy More
location 2453.
바이모어, 2453 위치에 보안 위험
Security breach at Buy More
location 2453.
바이모어, 2453 위치에 보안 위험
45분이면 다 돼
T-time is 45 minutes. What time
are your parents getting here?
부모님 언제 도착하신대?
Okay.
알겠어요
I love you, too.
저도 사랑해요
Babe...
자기 / 응?
I got some news.
할 말 있어
My parents can't make it.
우리 부모님 못 오신대
Don't toy with my emotions
right now, Devon.
지금은 그런 장난 치지마, 데븐
내가 어떻게
감히 장난을 치겠어
Honey, I wouldn't dare.
- You're serious?
- Yeah.
정말이야?
응 / 정말 잘됐다!
Oh, that's great!
Oh, that's so great!
진짜 잘됐어!
- Oh, my God.
- Now can we just have some fun?
어쩜 좋아 / 그럼 이제
재밌게 놀아볼까?
- Yes!
- Listen to Chuck's stories.
응! / 척 얘기도 듣고
Laugh at Morgan as he o-faces through
his, his mashed potatoes and stuffing.
모건이 입에 뭐 넣고
좋아 죽는거 보고 웃고
아 맞다
Oh, no!
I uninvited Morgan.
나 모건 초대 안했어
He's like the one person who
loves this dinner more than everyone.
누구보다 이 저녁시간을
기다렸을 앤데..
Ah, man, some animals
got in the trash again.
또 짐승이 쓰레기통 뒤지나봐
버리는거 봤거든요
Well, I saw you put it in the bag.
아직은 먹어도
괜찮을거 같아서요
You know, and I figured
it was still gonna be good.
So I...
그래서..
Okay.
알았어요
모건, 초대 안해서 정말 미안해
Morgan, I'm so sorry that
I uninvited you to Thanksgiving.
제발, 부디 날 용서해
Please, please forgive me.
Forgive you? Yeah, of course.
용서해요?
네 당연하죠
Yes, I understand.
I completely understand.
네 이해해요
정말 이해해요
요즘 스트레스 많이
받았을거 아니예요
I mean, you've been so stressed
out with this whole thing
and, you know, with our
new boss at work
직장엔 새 보스도 왔지
척하고 질은 또..
and this Chuck and Jill thing is like...
척하고 질이라니?
What Chuck and Jill thing?
질이요?
전 아무 말도 안했..
What Jill thing?
I didn't say anything...
Morgan, you tell me
everything that you know.
모건, 알고 있는거
빠짐없이 다 털어놔
Absolutely, I will.
물론이죠. 그럴게요
그럼 제 작은
부탁 하나 들어주실래요?
Can I just get one small favor?
I need to invite a couple guests over.
두 명 더 초대해주세요
척?
Chuck?
Hey.
??
혹시 물 같은거
필요없나해서 와봤어
I was just seeing if you, you know,
if you needed a water or something.
아니야 괜찮아
No, I'm good.
케이시하고 새라가
다시 시작하겠대?
Are Casey and Sarah ready
to start again?
아니
no.
아직 아니야
No, not just yet.
But before they do, I was wondering if
I could maybe ask you a few things.
하지만 그 전에
내가 몇 가지
물어봐도 될까
이거 어떻게 쓰는건지 알아?
Do you know how to work
all this stuff?
응 당연하지
Yeah, totally.
I, uh, read the manual.
설명서 읽었어
You read a lie detector manual?
거짓말 탐지기
설명서를 읽었다고?
No, this is the manual
for the entire Castle base.
아니. 이 기지 설명서야
기지 설명서를 읽었다고?
you read a manual for a base?
응, 그래, 그게..
Well, you know, I mean, um...
대충 훑어봤어
...I skimmed it.
내가, 내가 몇 가지
물어봐도 될까?
Would you, uh,
would you mind if I ask you
a couple questions?
물어봐
Go ahead.
스탠포드 다닐 때
Back at Stanford,
우리 둘이 사귈 때
when we were dating,
진심이었어?
was that for real?
응
Yes.
??
날 정말 좋아했어?
You really liked me?
진심이었어?
Those were real emotions?
응
Yes.
??
근데 왜 내가 학교에서
쫓겨나자마자 브라이스랑 잔거야?
Okay, then, well then
why did you sleep with Bryce
right after I got kicked
out of school?
Chuck, it has to be a "yes" or
"no" question or it won't work.
척. 대답이 네, 아니오인
질문을 해야지
브라이스도 사랑했어?
Did you love him, too?
아니
No.
??
잘됐네
Great.
That's great.
That makes it even worse.
정말 잘됐어
상황이 더 나빠졌어
네가 안 물어보는 질문이 있잖아
There's a question
you're not asking.
바로 네 앞에 있는데
묻지 않고 있어
It's right there,
and you're not asking it.
브라이스하고 잤어?
Did you sleep with Bryce?
아니
No.
I didn't.
안잤어
??
모두 꼼짝마!
Everyone freeze!
멈춰
??
다 밖으로 끌어내
Take 'em all out of here.
여기 이 놈만 빼고
Except this one on the table.
He's mine.
얜 내꺼야
지난 6년동안 난 네가
So you're telling me that for
the last six years of my life
I've been believing that you
betrayed me. Why would you do that?
날 배신한거라고 생각했어
왜 그런거야?
네가 학교에서 쫓겨났을 때
When you got kicked out of school,
풀크럼에서 나보고
널 놓아줘야한다고 했어
my FULCRUM advisor said
that I had to let you go.
널 브라이스랑 떼놓기 위해선
Now you weren't talking to Bryce,
so that was the easiest way to do it.
그게 유일한 방법이었으니까
I'm so sorry, Chuck.
정말 미안해, 척
이건 말도 안돼
I don't believe this.
풀크럼에서 날 차라고 했다고?
FULCRUM told you to dump me?
다른 방법이 없었어
I didn't have a choice.
날 죽이라는 명령을 받았는데도
넌 그러지 않았어
I guess in your defense,
when they told you to kill me,
you didn't do it. So,
뭔가 의미가 있는거겠지
I guess that means something.
맞아
It does.
I never wanted to hurt you,
Chuck, ever.
널 해치고 싶진 않았어, 척
You were my first love.
네가 내 첫사랑이니까
이 일이 모두 끝나면
Do you think that
when this is all over,
우리 다시 잘 해볼수 있을까?
we could try again?
이것 좀 풀어줘
Get me out of these.
응
Yes.
??
척, 리더를 잡았어요
Chuck, we have Leader.
지금 기지로 데려갈거예요
We're taking him back to Castle.
Great. See you when you get back.
잘됐네요. 돌아오면 봐요
I'm sorry, Chuck.
미안해 척
척?
Chuck?
- 척, 무슨 일 있어요?
- 다치지 않게 하겠다고 약속했어
Chuck, what's the matter?
You promised that
you wouldn't hurt them.
총은 탁자 위에 두고
수갑 풀어줘
Put the guns on the table,
take the cuffs off now.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I let her out.
It's my fault. I'm sorry.
미안해요 미안해요
제가 풀어줬어요
제 잘못이예요. 미안해요
Now, I believe we were headed
to a holding area.
우리 아까 창고로
가는 중인것 같던데
Show me the way.
창고로 가지
척, 시키는대로만 해
그럼 다 괜찮을거야
Chuck, do what he says
and you'll be okay.
내 친구들은?
What about my friends?
Just do what he says.
시키는대로 해
How could you do this, Jill?
네가 어떻게 이럴수 있어?
Chuck, it's complicated.
척, 복잡한 사정이 있어
나도 복잡한건 알아
알겠어?
Listen, I know complicated, okay?
How could you do this?
다른사람도 아니고
어떻게 네가 이래?
자네 정말 수고했네
You did an excellent job, my dear.
합동 정보 데이터베이스에
접속해
Show him the access screen
for the Joint Intelligence Database.
미안한데
어떻게 하는지 몰라
I'm sorry. I don't know how to do that.
당장 하지 않으면
친구들이 죽게될거야
Do it now or I'll kill your friends,
starting with the blonde.
금발부터 시작해주지
Thank you, Chuck.
고맙네 척
다 거짓이었지?
This was all a trick, wasn't it?
I mean, you guys just did all this just
to get in here and access our computer.
다 여기 들어와서 컴퓨터에
접근하려고 꾸민 짓인거야
그렇다고 널 쏘라고 하다니
Y-You, you let her shoot you.
Devious, aren't we? Move him.
우리 똑똑하지?
가둬
Oh, baby.
Jill, you're making a big mistake.
질, 큰 실수 하는거야
난 시키는대로 하는 수밖에 없어
I have to do what he says, Chuck.
왜? 왜? 대체 저 사람은
뭘 찾고 있는건데?
Why? Why? What is
your boss searching for?
무슨 기밀이길래
이렇게까지해?
I mean, what,
what secret is worth this?
He's searching for someone.
사람을 찾고 있는거야
누굴? / 브라이스 라킨
- Who?
- Bryce Larkin.
브라이스?
Bryce?
브라이스는 왜 찾아?
Why are you looking for Bryce?
척, 모르는척 할거 없어
Chuck, don't try and protect him.
We know he's CIA.
CIA인거 다 아니까
우리 물건을 훔쳐갔어
He stole something from us.
They're looking for the Intersect.
인터섹트를 찾고 있는거야
미안해요 새라
I'm sorry, Sarah.
I should have listened to you.
당신 얘길 안 들어서요
We'll figure something out.
- 방법을 찾아낼거예요
- 사실 생각해둔게 있어요
Actually, I have a plan.
Hey, what are you doing?
뭐하는거예요?
That's the Castle manual.
I told you that's top secret.
저거 기지 설명서야
내가 극비 사항이라고 했을텐데
Yeah, I know.
네 알아요
저도잖아요
So am I.
척
Chuck.
What did you do?
무슨 짓을 한거야?
Like I told Jill,
I read the manual.
질한테도 얘기했지만
설명서를 읽어뒀거든
What... did you do?
뭘 했냐니까?
Well, I locked you
out of the computer system
이 기지에 있는
모든 방에 설치된
원격 제어 콘솔로
컴퓨터 시스템을 잠궈버렸지
using the remote console that every
room in Castle is equipped with.
설명서 안에 써 있더라고
It's in the manual.
안타깝게도
설명서는 내가 갖고 있고
Unfortunately, said manual
is in here with me,
and since I overrode
Castle's primary controls,
기지의 주된 통제권을
갖고 있으니
우린 여기 방탄유리가 설치된 방에서
안전하게 있게 된거지
we're now safely locked
within these bulletproof cells.
나 똑똑하지?
Devious, aren't I?
I'll make one call and my men
will be here in 20 minutes.
내가 전화 한 통만 하면
20분내로 사람이 올거야
먼저 그 얘길
꺼내줘서 고마워
I'm so glad you brought that up
내가 통신 제어 장치도
작동시켜뒀거든
because I also activated the
base's communications jammer,
그래서 전화도 못 걸어
미안
so no calls out--
sorry about that--
또 CIA 이상경보장치도
작동시켰거든
and because I triggered
the CIA's trouble alarm,
I think the cavalry's going
to be here in ten minutes or so.
기병대에서 10분정도후면
도착할껄
The nerd in me really, really wants
to say "Checkmate" right about now.
내 머리속에서 "체크메이트"라고
외쳐달라고 난리다
(척이 이겼다는 얘기)
그러지마
Never say that.
- 왜?
- 누구랑 게임을 하는지 모르는 모양인데
Why?
Because you don't know
who you're playing against.
이 방이 방탄은 될지 모르겠지만
These cells might be bulletproof,
이건 못 견뎌낼껄
but they can't withstand that.
The blast will kill them,
but I'll bet your cell will be fine.
폭발하면 네 친구들은
다 죽게 될거야
하지만 넌 멀쩡하겠지
Chuck, don't do anything.
척, 아무 짓도 하지 말아요
Stay in that cell, Bartowski.
거기 그대로 있어
- Jill?
- Just do what he says, Chuck.
- 질?
- 시키는대로 해, 척
문 열어
Open the door
or your friends will die.
아님 네 친구들은 죽어
잘가게, 바토스키
Good-bye, Mr. Bartowski.
기다려!
W-W-W-W-Wait! Wait.
기다려
??
자, 이제
나가는 길을 알려줘
Now, show me the way out of here.
Jill, if you hurt him, I swear...
질, 척 털끝 하나 건드리기만 해봐
가만 안둬
It's a message from Chuck.
척이 보낸 메시지야
??
그 쪽 문도 열었어요
바이모어로 데려갈게요
케이시를 거기로 보내요
???
Drop it!
총 버려!
새라! 쏘지 마요!
Sarah, don't hurt her!
Jill, Jill.
질, 질
내가 도와줄게
Hey, I can help you.
날 따라와
Come with me.
Come on.
어서
You thought you were
going to take me down?
네가 날 이길 수 있을줄 알았나?
아니 내가 해주지!
No, baby, I am!
도둑놈들이 너무 싫어
I hate thieves.
Grimes put you in charge?
모건이 시켰나?
네
Yeah.
똑똑하군
Smart boy.
뭘 하려고?
What's going on?
- What are we doing?
- Look...
여긴 왜 온거야?
너 매트릭스 봤지?
you're taking the Matrix, okay?
전륜구동에
터치 스크린 네비게이션
All-wheel drive, touch screen navi,
iPod capability, and a full tank of gas.
아이팟도 되고
기름도 가득있어
완벽한 도주 차량이야
It's the perfect getaway car.
어서 타서
최대한 멀리 도망쳐
Just get in
and drive as far as you can.
I won't call it in, I swear.
보고 안 할테니까
고마워
Thank you.
나랑 같이 가
Come with me.
We can still be together.
아직 우리
함께 할 수 있어
어떻게?
How?
Just you and me.
No secrets, no spies.
우리 단 둘이서
더이상 비밀도
스파이짓도 없이
같이 가자, 척
Come with me, Chuck.
No, I, I can't. I can't. I...
아니, 못 해
난 못 가
우리처럼 정반대인 사람들끼리
서로 끌린다는거..
look, obviously, there's the whole
"opposites attract" chemistry thing
that we have, and I, I...
문제가 하나 있어
it's just the-there's,
there's one small problem.
척, 뭐하는거야?
What are you doing, Chuck?
??
뭐하는거야?
이러지마, 척
What's going on?
Don't do this to me, Chuck.
난 분명 돕고싶다고 했어
You should know I wanted to help you.
I was going to let you get away.
널 그냥 놓아주려고 했었어
Chuck, no.
척, 이러지마
But when you were
about to kill Sarah,
하지만 네가
새라를 죽이려고 했을 때
네가 나 대신
결정을 내려준거야
you made the decision for me.
You're under arrest, Jill,
질. 널 체포한다
and I'm breaking up with you.
그리고
우리 헤어져
I'm sorry, Sarah.
미안해요 새라
I should have listened
to you from the beginning.
처음부터 새라 말을
들었어야 했어요
당신 말이 맞았어요
아직 준비가 안 됐었어요
You were right:
I wasn't ready for this mission.
이런 임무에 준비가 될
사람은 아무도 없을거예요, 척
No one is ready for this type
of mission, Chuck.
Your girlfriend being FULCRUM isn't
something they teach you in spy school.
애인이 풀크럼 요원이란건
스파이 양성소에서도 가르쳐 주지 않아요
I'm just too trusting.
사람을 너무 믿나봐요
어렸을 때 부터
Ever since I was a kid,
사람들이 하는 말은
모조리 믿었어요
I really wanted to believe what
everybody always told me. You know?
I'm just getting used to this new
job-- all the spying and lying.
스파이에 거짓말까지
새로운 일에 점점 익숙해져가요
익숙해지지 마요
Don't get used to it.
What makes you special is that
you're not like every other spy.
그게 당신이 다른 스파이들과
달리 특별한 이유니까요
척은 좋은 사람이고
사람들을 돕고 싶어하잖아요
You're a good guy,
and you want to help people.
날 속일 생각은 말아요
Leave the deception to me.
새라가 있어서 다행이예요
I'm glad I have you.
Yeah, we're better as a team.
네. 우린 팀 일때가 더 좋아요
Oh, yeah.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Can I borrow you?
Sorry, I'm stealing him real quick.
나랑 얘기 좀 할까?
미안. 금방이면 돼
이젠 질하고 척이
안 만나는게 확실해?
Are you absolutely certain
that Jill is not with Chuck?
Yeah, I mean, that's what he,
that's what he tol...
네, 척이 저한테는
그렇게 말했어요
Why, you think that Chuck's
gonna break up with Sarah?
새라랑 헤어질 것 같아요?
나야 안 그랬음 좋겠지
Well, I hope not.
Yeah, me, too.
네, 저도요
우리한테 필요한게
뭔지 아세요?
You know what we need here?
- 뭔데?
- 추수감사절의 기적이요
- What?
- Thanksgiving miracle.
아니 들어봐요
Yeah, y-y-yeah, listen.
척하고 새라는
저 문으로 들어와서
Chuck and Sarah are gonna
walk through that door,
모두 행복하게 보내고
they're going to be
as happy as can be,
다 괜찮아질거예요
and everything's going to be fine.
대단한데 모건
good job, Morgan.
Hi.
안녕하세요
I could have asked for anything.
다른거 말할껄
- 추수감사절 잘 보내세요
- 왔네요. 새라도 잘 보내요
- Happy Thanksgiving.
- Hi. Happy Thanksgiving.
Ellie, uh, do you, do you realize that
누나, 저기 식탁에
레스터랑 제프 있는거 봤지?
Lester and Jeff of the Nerd Herd
are at our table right now?
무슨 일 있어?
Is everything okay?
데븐네 부모님이
못 오신다고 하시길래
Yes, well, the Awesomes couldn't
make it, so you know me--
나 알잖아
여럿이서 즐겁게 보내려고
just expand Thanksgiving.
- Okay.
- Happy Thanksgiving.
추수감사절 잘 보내요
You, too.
레스터도요
Are you okay?
괜찮은거지?
Of course, yeah. Why, why do you ask?
응, 물론이지
그건 왜 물어?
Well, because Morgan told me
about you and Jill.
모건이 너랑 질 얘길 해줬어
I'm sorry. I just...
I was worried about you.
미안해. 누난..
네가 걱정돼서
아니야 괜찮아
no, yeah, everything's good.
우리가 다시 한번 만나서
She wanted to see if we could work it
out and maybe give it a second try.
- 잘 해보고 싶어하더라고
- 그래서?
And?
And I realized that Jill,
Stanford, and Bryce--
질이나 스탠포드,
브라이스 일 모두
that's the story from my past.
내 과거에 있던 일이잖아
하지만 지금은
누나도 있고 새라도 있고 또..
But my new story is
you and Sarah and these...
frigging yahoos.
망할 친구놈들도 있잖아
그게 가끔은
And sometimes...
it can be a really fun story.
정말 정말 재밌거든
스웨덴 비키니 팀
Uh, Swedish bikini team.
드로리언, 날아다니는 드로리언
(영화 백투더 퓨처에나오는 날라다니는 차)
- DeLorean, flying DeLorean.
- Hey, Morgan.
모건
Come on, buddy.
어서 와
어쨌든
내가 무슨 얘기중이었지?
So anyways, where was I?
Yeah, you were saying how,
how the turkey gets made.
칠면조를 어떻게 만들었는지요
칠면조가 자길 먹어달랬다고
You were saying that
the turkeys volunteer.
No, they don't.
It's more of a draft.
Toast to, uh, some of the great,
faces that I know
익숙한 사람들과
추수감사절에 새로온 사람들을 위해 건배
and some new ones to Thanksgiving.
Yeah, we don't know each other.
그래 우리 서로 모르잖아
Hear, hear.
건배
Happy Thanksgiving.
다들 추수감사절 잘 보내요
Great job, babe.
수고했어 엘리
영문자막 : www.shooter.cn
싱크편집 / 한글번역
김호정(hojeong_@nate.com)
피드백은 메일로 보내주세요
수정금지 / 배포자유
자막제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://club.nate.com/24)